{"test_questions": [[{"question": "ODL supports which of the following types of association relationships?", "opta": "Unary", "optb": "Unary and Binary", "optc": "Unary and Binary and Ternary", "optd": "Unary and Binary and Ternary and higher", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An extent is which of the following?", "opta": "A keyword that indicates that the subclass inherits from a superclass", "optb": "A keyword that indicates that the superclass inherits from a subclass", "optc": "The set of all instances of a class within a database", "optd": "Only one instance of a class within a database", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Identify the class name for the following code: ABC123 course();", "opta": "ABC123", "optb": "course", "optc": "course()", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Using ODL, you can define which of the following?", "opta": "Attribute", "optb": "Structure", "optc": "Operation", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The keyword \"inverse\" is used in which of the following?", "opta": "Class", "optb": "Attribute", "optc": "Relationship", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The object definition language (ODL) is which of the following?", "opta": "Used to develop logical schemas", "optb": "A data definition language for OODB", "optc": "A method to implement a logical schema", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An atomic literal is which of the following?", "opta": "Strings", "optb": "Boolean", "optc": "Long", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning an ODBMS?", "opta": "They have the ability to store complex data types on the Web.", "optb": "They are overtaking RDBMS for all applications.", "optc": "They are most useful for traditional, two-dimensional database table applications.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The reserved word enum is used for which of the following?", "opta": "To define a range for an attribute.", "optb": "To define a range for a class.", "optc": "To define a range for a relationship.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is an unordered collection of elements that may contain duplicates?", "opta": "Set", "optb": "Bag", "optc": "List", "optd": "Dictionary", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning the following statement: class Manager extends Employee", "opta": "Manager is a concrete class and a superclass.", "optb": "Manager is a concrete class and a subclass.", "optc": "Manager is an abstract class and a superclass.", "optd": "Manager is an abstract class and a subclass.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is an ordered collection of elements of the same type?", "opta": "Set", "optb": "Bag", "optc": "List", "optd": "Dictionary", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A relationship should be specified how in the ODL?", "opta": "One direction starting with the first class", "optb": "One direction starting with the second class", "optc": "Neither direction.", "optd": "Both directions.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Using OQL, you may do which of the following?", "opta": "Return an entire collection of elements including duplicates.", "optb": "Return a collection of elements without duplicates.", "optc": "Return a specific subset of elements using a given criteria.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Object Query Language is which of the following\"?", "opta": "Similar to SQL and uses a select-from-where structure", "optb": "Similar to SQL and uses a select-where structure", "optc": "Similar to SQL and uses a from-where structure", "optd": "Not similar to SQL", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}